<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Stylo</string>

    //Headings
    <string name="heading_one">Stylo</string>
    <string name="heading_two">Treat Yourself</string>
    <string name="heading_three">Change Up The Look</string>

    //Description
    <string name="desc_one">Fashion Tips &amp; Trick. Be Comfy and Confident in your Style.</string>
    <string name="desc_two">Treat your self as you would treat others</string>
    <string name="desc_three">How you look is the least interesting about you</string>

    //Description Tips and Trick
    <string name="desc_tips_and_trick">Some days we just want to look our best, and your clothes are obviously a huge part of that.  But, what you may not know is that clothes and styling techniques can teach you how to look taller and slimmer.

This post is not about dieting or endorsing a culture that praises the skinny body type.  But rather it is taking your body shape, and your clothes and giving you the most flattering outfit inspirations and style tips.

I use these tips fairly regularly, but let’s not forget there are days where our outfits just won’t be picture-worthy and that is ok too.  So before I teach you how to dress to look slim and tall, let’s accept ourselves for exactly how we are day-to-day.

I want to look taller and slimmer, is that ok?
Yes, absolutely!  Just like makeup enhances your natural beauty, the following style tips will enhance your style and body shape.  I am not endorsing losing weight, fad diets, or any exercise program to look taller and slimmer.

These are styling techniques that will give you a streamlined look that highlights your best assets and keeps you from making fashion mistakes that are aging your or unflattering.

Look at these tips as building upon your natural figure, and giving you some extra confidence, rather than any sort of deceptive practice.

And, even if you don’t want to specifically dress to look tall and slim, these tips will help you improve your style by highlighting your best features, and avoiding frumpy proportions. </string>

    <string name="detail_description">Lorem It is a long established fact that a reader will be distracted by the readable content of a page when looking at its layout. The point of using. more</string>
</resources>